Marc HAGE

Web Programming Amsterdam

Hi, my name is Marc Hage. I've always worked with web languages. I love coding, keeping things simple and/or adhering to technical standards. I used to steer clear of javascript/ecmascript. Now it is the opposite.

Also proficient in Photoshop and to a lesser extent Illustrator

marc.hage@me.com

- --
- https://marchage.github.io/
- marchage
- Js Javascript-ing in various forms, e.g. front-end, backend, or greacemonkey
- > shell scripting and thus server maintenance
- digital automation
- pretty interfaces

Experience

Programmer

Datlinq | Sendsteps | Atabix | MARC-IT since July 2006, with intermezzo's Javascript/php programmer, sometimes freelance

Test engineer

Sogeti

July 2010 - December 2011 tester, web pen-tester.

Sales clerk

V & D | Perla Kantoor | Phones H'stede

1998 - 2006

Part-time sales clerk

Education

Bachelor of Science

2001 - 2010

Computer science, VU Amsterdam, The Netherlands.

TMap Next

July 2010 - September 2010

Includig business course at Ohio University (US).

<>> Projects

Running a part-time business

Typo3, PHP, HTML-CSS, Flash-ActionScript, Ubuntu, Windows, OSX, PhotoShop

Servicing clients' IT needs.

Quaestoraat College Chaos, Unitas Amsterdam

Excel, Word

Comptroller for a 1 year term.

Skills



Contributions

(None)

No worth-mentioning open source contributions https://github.com/marchage